Dan Anthony D. Angeles

Software Engineer

Email: angeles_dondee@yahoo.com

Phone: 0421-168-015

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/dan-

anthony-angeles-95880a79/

Software Engineering Experience in building and maintaining websites and other software for industries in banking, communications, insurance institutions, and digital marketing. Highly Skilled in .Net through .Net Core and .Net Framework using VB.Net, C#. Also knowledgeable in RDBMS and SQL through Teradata. Interested in FullStack Software Engineering and Test Automation. I was assessed by ACS under ANZSCO Code 261313 (Software Engineer)

Skills and Knowledge

Technologies

- .Net Core 6
- .Net Framework 4.8
- C# and VB.Net
- Typescript, HTML, CSS
- Teradata and SQL
- Java JDK and Maven
- Python Scripting Language
- VBA
- Sharepoint PowerApps

Tools

- Microsoft Visual Studio
- IntelliJ
- Eclipse
- JIRA
- VMWare
- Postman

Version Control

- Git Hub
- SVN

Environment

- Windows
- Unix/Linux

Management Framework

- Scrum
- Agile
- Waterfall

Certifications

- Teradata Vantage Certified Associate (2018)
- Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals (2020)
- N5 Certified Japanese
 Language Proficient

Education

 De la Salle University (2005-2010), Graduate of Bachelor of Science in Manufacturing Engineering and Management Major in Mechatronics and Robotics

Professional Work Experience

Eclaro International Philippines Inc. (2018/04 – 2023/06) Formerly Teradata GCC Philippines Inc.

Software Engineer

- Spearheaded the web application migration from .Net Framework to .Net Core 6 using **C#**.
- Developed and released the first RESTful Web API of our existing web application in VB.Net.
- Developed new features performed bug fixes on the frontend of our web application using **Typescript**, **HTML** and **CSS**.
- Developed SQL scripts used in our web application in **Teradata RDBMS.**
- Spearheaded a dashboard development project using **Python's Plotly, Dash APIs**, and **Flask** virtual environment.
- Used JIRA for user stories, sprint tracking and bug tracking.
- Used **Git Hub** and **SVN** for versioning control of software patch releases.
- Developed new functionalities and performed bug fixes.
- Created and designed functional specifications of the web application and web APIs.
- Managed, investigated, and answered client queries.
- Mentored and trained new hires in project-specific training.

DevOps/Automation Engineer

- Developed a front-end test automation tool with automated test results document generation in **Java Selenium** used in testing web applications.
- Developed a report extraction automation tool in Java Selenium that effectively performs data mining and analysis used in digital marketing.
- Developed a test automation tool in **VBA** that significantly reduced the review process time of our data migration scripts and documents by 50%.

RedPoint Global Inc. (2013/10 – 2017/11)

Java SDK Developer

 Developed rapid prototypes of proof-of-concept plug-ins being integrated in RedPoint Data Management Software using Java.
 APIs used are Azure Cloud, Cassandra No SQL, Google Cloud, SalesForce, and

O-Authentication.

Automated Test Engineer

- Developed automated tests executed via Unix Shell Scripts in testing the RedPoint Data Management Software.

Canon Information Technologies Philippines Inc. (2010/05 – 2013/07)

Hardware Engineer

- Developed firmware-like automated test codes in Specman E, run regression tests and collect source code coverage to test and verify RTL design and systems using black box testing method.
- Created documentation for test cases, testing strategy, and test results.
- Committed and released coded tests, testbenches, models, and monitors to the project's version control manager.